(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T22:47:19.072720",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ：応援セット、マフラータオル
Second-Batch Merchandise: Support Set & Muffler Towel
2次販売グッズ：ペンライト、Tシャツ、缶バッジ
Second-Batch Merchandise: Penlight, T-shirt, & Badges
2次販売グッズ：アクリルスタンド、ストラップ、リュック
Second-Batch Merchandise: Acrylic Stand, Strap, & Backpack
2次販売グッズ：アクリルパネル
Second-Batch Merchandise: Acrylic Panel
3期生への応援メッセージ
Support Messages for the 3rd Generation
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK!
2次販売グッズ 応援セット 推進マフラータオル
[2nd Wave Merch] Support Set & Character Muffler Towels
だから
So...
君のこと大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛きっときっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely, surely won't stop!
I I I I love you 君
I, I, I, I love you...
あいあいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー
I-I-I-I♡I love you!
あいにじゅー
I need you!
もっと もっと
More! More!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want!
揺れるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My swaying heart is going hop, hop, hop!
穴に落ちてあびゃあびゃ
Falling into a hole, screaming "Abya-bya!"
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't escape!
どうしたもんかね ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui-nui-nui!
助けて君たぴ ahoy hoy
Save me, Kimitapi! Ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと
More! More!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
＃きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推してかない？〜
[Title: Operation Kyururun ~Won't you support the strongest idols?~]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
協賛
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I fell in love with anime and really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎて辛いっ！
...is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
ジョイサウンド！
JOYSOUND!
ホロライブ3期生プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are now rolling out!
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet Plushies
寝そべりミニマスコット
Lay-down Mini Mascots
大判マウスパッド
Oversized Mousepad
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね♪
Get them at amusement centers nationwide!
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya!
ぎゅう
Beef!
ぎゅう、ぎゅう
Beef, beef!
ぎゅう
Beef!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Enjoy the devotion of the original.
牛丼は吉野家
When it comes to beef bowls, Yoshinoya is the one.
やっぱりこれだね
This is definitely the best!
ホロライブ3期生ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Gen Mini CD Collection
ライブ会場販売！
On sale at the concert venue!
つながるくるりえますこっと
Connecting Kururie Mascots
全国のガシャポン自販機にて発売予定
Coming soon to Gashapon machines nationwide!
きゅるるん大作戦
[Operation Kyururun]
本日は ホロライブ
Today, Hololive...
サードジェネレーションライブ「きゅるるん大作戦 最強アイドル！推ししか勝たんオーディション」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to 3rd Generation Live: "Operation Kyururun: Strongest Idol! Only My Oshie Wins Audition"!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show until the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of video recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の、みんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Moshing, diving, and throwing objects onto the stage are strictly prohibited, as they cause trouble for others and disrupt the show.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信および、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Additionally, cameras for video streaming and photography are inside the venue, and the audience may be captured.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware in advance that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#きゅるるん大作戦Day2」です。
Also, the official hashtag for the live is #KyururunDaisakusenDay2.
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてくだい。
Use the hashtag to hype up the show!
それでは、開演まであと少しです。
Well then, we are just moments away from the start.
君たちの声をいっぱい聴かせてください！
Let us hear your loud voices!
そして！今からちょっと、3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが…
And! We're planning to do a huddle with the 3rd Gen members right now...
えっ、マイクを通さずやりますので、ちょっと静かにして、耳を澄ませていただきたい。
We'll be doing it without microphones, so please be quiet and listen closely.
いくんで、ちょっとしんと待っててくださいね。いきます！
We're about to do it, so please keep it dead silent and wait. Here we go!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
おー！
Yeah!
hololive 3rd Generation Live
兎田ぺこら
[Usada Pekora]
不知火フレア
[Shiranui Flare]
白銀ノエル
[Shirogane Noel]
宝鐘マリン
[Houshou Marine]
#きめるるん大作戦
[#Kimerurun Daisakusen]
超アイドル伝説のガールは欲張り
The girls of the super idol legend are greedy,
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
smiling together and becoming even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
遠いお出かけ覚悟して
Be prepared for a long trip,
他人なのに家族みたいで
even though we're strangers, we're like family.
ラブ＆ライク アダプタレーション
Love & like adaptation,
ルール＆ライフ セッション
Rule & life session,
色々あるけど手足してさ
Although there are many things, let's join hands...
でっかくなっていきたいよね
...and we want to grow bigger, right?
demo chitchana koto mo daiji ni shite
But let's also cherish the small things.
1つ
One,
2つ
Two,
刻んでいく
carving our path,
楽しんで触れるのが嬉しい
I'm happy to joyfully connect.
ベタからのエンターテイナー
Entertainers starting from clichés.
後ろだって見えてる
We can see even the back rows,
画面の向こうも届いてる
we're reaching the other side of the screen too.
光の海を泳ぐの
Let's swim through the ocean of lights!
超アイドル伝説のガールは欲張り
The girls of the super idol legend are greedy,
愛されたいし認めて欲しいし 欲張らなきゃやだ
wanting to be loved and acknowledged, we must be greedy!
清楚超絶狙い撃ちで君にウインク
Targeting you with a super pure wink!
やっぱ伝説のガールでめっちゃハッピー
As expected, being the legendary girls makes us so happy,
応援もしたいし恋もしたいし 叶っちゃうやった
wanting to support and fall in love, they all come true, yay!
全力走る 夢中な君と
Running at full speed with you, who is absorbed,
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
smiling together and becoming even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
せっかくだからやりきりたいし
Since we're here, we want to give it our all,
乗り越えるべき壁もデカい
the wall we must overcome is also huge.
トライ＆アンド エンターテイン
Try & and entertain,
みんなを想ってるようで ずっと君のことを想ってる
Though it seems I think about everyone, I'm always thinking about you.
どうかな？
What do you think?
憧れた夢には近づけてるかな？
Am I getting closer to the dream I yearned for?
声は涙を超えるから頑張れるんだ 聞かせて
Because my voice overcomes tears, I can do my best! Let me hear it!
もっと最高！
Even more awesome!
超アイドル伝説のガールは幸せ
The girls of the super idol legend are happy,
愛されて生きる伸び代あって 下向くとこやだ
being loved, with room to grow, we hate looking down!
テンポアップし続けていく
We'll keep stepping up the tempo,
見たい景色へ
toward the scenery we want to see!
世界に発信
Broadcast to the world!
世界にアピール
Appeal to the world!
世界よりダンシン
Dancing more than the world!
今すぐ達成
Accomplish it right now!
みんなで作っていく
We will build it together!
イェーイ
Yeah!
もっともっと盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get even more hyped up!
君たち、まだまだ声出せますよね！
You guys, you can still scream, right?!
うつむいても
Even if I look down...
がんばっちゃう！
...I'll do my best!
褒められて伸びるタイプなんです、よね？
I'm the type who grows when praised, right?
この空間が宝物
This space is a treasure...
めげちゃわないよ、笑って！
...so I won't get discouraged, smile!
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドル！
Super idols!
天性のガールはよくばり
Natural-born girls are greedy...
愛されたいし 夢だって見たい 君とじゃなくちゃ やだっ！
...we want to be loved and dream, it has to be with you or no way!
って、ご調子者です
Well, we're just getting carried away!
狙い撃ちで君にウインク
Targeting you with a wink!
やっぱ天性のガールで めっちゃハッピー
As expected of natural-born girls, we're super happy!
あれもしたいし これもしたいし 叶っちゃう、やったー！
I want to do this and that, and they'll all come true, yay!
先頭走る もちろん君と
Running at the front, of course, with you...
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
...laughing together and becoming even cuter!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like we can go anywhere...
Oh yeah, yeah!
今日はこのまま さようならじゃないよ
Today is not goodbye just like this.
手をとってくれたなら
If you would take my hand...
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
...into a night where even secrets fall asleep...
君を連れていくよ
...I will take you away.
それはたとえ遠く離れてたって
Even if we are far apart...
手を繋いでいられるような
...so we can keep holding hands...
奇跡のような話をしよう
...let's talk about a story like a miracle.
窓はあけといて
Leave the window open.
今日までを思い出して
Remembering everything up to today...
ひとつひとつ並べたら
...if we line them up one by one...
明日の雨が気になりだして
...I start to worry about tomorrow's rain...
とても眠れないみたいだ
...and it seems I can't fall asleep at all.
変わりたくないことや
The things I don't want to change...
変わらなきゃいけないことも
...and the things that must change...
少しずつ忘れたまま
...while gradually forgetting them...
窓の外眺めていたんだ
...I was gazing out the window.
雨が降り出すその前に
Before the rain starts to fall...
君のところまで行けるような気がして
...I feel like I can make it to where you are...
目を閉じてみたんだ
...so I tried closing my eyes.
そして
And then...
このまま遠くへと行こう
...let's go far away just like this.
手をとってくれるかな
Will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Into a night where even secrets fall asleep...
君と泳いでいくよ
...I will swim through it with you.
街の灯りが消えるたびに笑って
Smiling every time the city lights go out...
路地裏でタッチしよう
...let's high-five in the back alley.
馬鹿みたいにさ
Like we're being silly...
話をしよう
...let's talk.
窓はあけといて
Leave the window open.
聞こえる
I can hear it...
...I can hear it.
次は マリン！
Next up is Marine!
起立！ 気をつけ！
Stand up! Attention!
3期生も盛り上がっていくよー！
The 3rd generation is also getting pumped up!
いい波乗って、マリン！
Ride a good wave, Marine!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like!
なんとかかんとかなんないかな (ラビラビ)
Can't we do something about this? (Labi-labi)
隣のあいつが邪魔だな (いかない！)
The one next to me is in the way (No way!)
そんなことダメダメだ
That's a no-no!
電撃勝負絶対
Definitely a blitzkrieg showdown!
とは言え 違う なんだって競争
But even so, it's different, everything's a competition!
逃げ出したら 終了
If you run away, it's over!
だんだんだんしん！
Dan-dan-dancing!
もちもち
Mochi-mochi!
電撃送信
Electric transmission!
サクッとサクッとシークレット
Quickly, quickly, it's a secret!
あの子には負けらんない
I can't lose to that girl!
際立ってじらじら
Standing out and teasing...
よくばりね
...how greedy!
よくばりか？
Are we greedy?
してやります！
I'll do it!
言わなくたってわかってる
Even if you don't say it, I know...
あーでもない こーでもない やめにしましょう
...this way or that way, let's stop all that.
つらぬいて マイマイマイマイ
Standing firm, my my my my...
引き下がりたくなーい！
...I don't want to back down!
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses...
ジタバタのユージュアル
...the usual struggling.
かんたんハニバニだりだりマジな話
Simple honey bunny, crazy, serious talk!
どっち どっち
Which one? Which one?
が好きなのよ
Do you like?
ダメダメダメダメ
No, no, no, no!
よそ見しないで
Don't look away!
ダメダメダメ
No, no, no!
抜け出しちゃいたい
I want to break free!
今日は私のほう
Today it's my turn!
一生一緒
Together forever...
どうしても反対方向
...somehow in opposite directions...
ワン、ツー、言い訳ばかり
...one, two, nothing but excuses!
いけしゃあしゃあと言い訳ばかりに 地団駄の優柔不断だんだん
You make shameless excuses all the time, stamping your feet in total indecision!
ハニガリガリガリ真面目な話 どっちどっちが好きなのよ？
Honey, let's talk seriously. Which one do you actually love?
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで
No, no, no! Don't look away!
ダメダメダメ もう逃げ出したい？
No, no, no! Do you want to run away already?
覚悟するしかないっしょ保存
You have no choice but to brace yourself!
逃がしません 反対方向
I won't let you escape in the other direction!
WANTED!
そばにいて 言い訳ばかり あぁ
Stay by my side, enough with the excuses, ah!
次はぺこら！
Next up is Pekora!
全力ジャンピングいくぺこらー！
Let's go, jumping with all our might, peko!
イェーイ！
Yay!
でも一歩駆けた眼差しで 歌いながら実る微笑へ
With a gaze that has taken a step forward, singing towards a ripening smile.
迷ってるの？ ボケっとしてるの？
Are you lost? Or are you just spacing out?
それは皆知らない
Nobody knows that anyway.
まだまだ楽しみたいじゃない
Don't we still want to keep having fun?
でもでも時間が足りない
But, but there's just not enough time!
ワクワクする明日へ
Towards an exciting tomorrow,
思い切って 振り切って 前向いてさぁ進もう
make the leap, shake it off, look forward, and let's go!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
歌って 本気で
Sing with all your heart!
踊り尽くしちゃえ
Dance until you can't dance anymore!
お空突き抜けちゃうくらいで
So high that we'll pierce right through the sky!
It's all right!
早起きよりも楽しんじゃおう
Let's just have fun, even more than waking up early!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because everything is bound to turn out fine!
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ GO
Since every pinch turns into a great opportunity!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all OK!
みんな笑えば無敵だね
If everyone smiles, we're totally invincible!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all OK!
またまた全力で
Once again, with all our might,
突き抜けちゃって
break right through!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's move forward with honest feelings!
ほっぷ・すてっぷ・じゃんぷで飛び出そう保存
Hop, step, jump, and leap out!
なかなかお布団から出られない
There are days when it's hard to get out of bed,
日もある でも明日から保存
but starting tomorrow...
そう明日から 本気を出すんだ
yes, starting tomorrow, I'll show my true power!
気が済むまで 日が暮れるまで
Until we're satisfied, until the sun goes down,
無限に楽しいし
it's infinitely fun!
It's all right!保存
It's all right!
早起きよりも楽しんじゃおう
Let's just have fun, even more than waking up early!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because everything is bound to turn out fine!
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ GO
Since every pinch turns into a great opportunity!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all OK!
みんな笑えば無敵だね
If everyone smiles, we're totally invincible!
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all OK!
またまた全力で
Once again, with all our might,
突き抜けちゃって
break right through!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's move forward with honest feelings!
ほっぷ・すてっぷ・じゃんぷで飛び出そう保存
Hop, step, jump, and leap out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
最後は、ノエル！
Last up is Noel!
はーい！みんな、シャッフルメドレー、最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Yeah! Everyone, let's keep the excitement going for the shuffle medley until the very end!
苦い恋の果て 残されたデッドゴールド 送り主不明の金の山
At the end of a bitter love, left with dead gold—a mountain of money from an unknown sender.
あいつの気配がするものは
Anything that carries a trace of him...
未練ばかりで食えやしない
...is filled with lingering regret and is completely useless.
私は生きながら 化けて出る 鏡の前で早変わり
I haunt this world while still alive, and quickly transform in front of the mirror.
バイバイ仮面でどうかしら 今宵もひと暴れ
How about a Bye-Bye Mask? Let's cause a scene again tonight!
踊れ 踊り踊り踊れ
Dance, dance, dance away!
乱れ髪 弾む胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing chest,
遠く鳴るのは波の音 酔いしれて
drowning in the distant sound of the waves.
射すスポット 射すスポット 射すスポットライトをみな
The spotlight, the spotlight... look at the spotlights shining down!
パイや パイや パパパヤパイ
Pai ya, pai ya, pa-pa-paya-pai!
バイバイ仮面は退屈よ
A Bye-Bye Mask is so boring!
パイや パイや パパパヤパイ
Pai ya, pai ya, pa-pa-paya-pai!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high!
ほーや！ ほーや！ ほーや！ 踊れよ
Hoya! Hoya! Hoya! Dance!
万歳万歳今夜は
Cheers, cheers to tonight!
せつなを生きるのよ
Live for the fleeting moment!
瞬間クライマックス
The momentary climax!
憂き世 忘れてふけるのよ
Forget this fleeting world and lose yourself!
ダッシングハイ
Dashing high!
ディスコティックに
In a discotheque style!
バイバイ仮面
Bye-Bye Mask!
パイや パイや パパパヤパイ
Pai ya, pai ya, pa-pa-paya-pai!
バイバイ仮面は退屈よ
A Bye-Bye Mask is so boring!
はい！
Yes!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high!
おどれ 魔法に おどれよ
Dance! Dance to the magic!
燦々 万歳 恋シャワー
Brilliant, cheers, shower of love!
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the moment!
春夏秋冬 クライマックス
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, climax!
浮世忘れて 耽るダンス はい はい
Forget the transient world and indulge in dance, yes, yes!
ディスコティーク・クイーン
Discotheque Queen
パイパイ仮面
Pai Pai Kamen!
ディスコティーク・クイーン
Discotheque Queen
パイパイ仮面
Pai Pai Kamen!
いぇーい！
Yay!
いぇーい！ありがとうー！
Yay! Thank you!
Day 2! Day 2!
Day 2始まったよー！
Day 2 has begun!
いぇーい！
Yay!
じゃあ早速自己紹介からしていきましょうか！
Well then, shall we start with introductions?
していきましょう！
Let's do it!
じゃあ、みんなぺこーら久しぶりのあの挨拶いくから
Alright, everyone, I'm going to do my greeting for the first time in a while...
わかるよねみんな！あの挨拶だよ！
...so you all know it, right? That greeting!
どの挨拶だ？ あれだ、あれだ！
Which greeting? That one!
あれしかない！ いくよ！
There's only one! Here we go!
とどんとどんとんどん！全人類VTuber...
To-don to-don ton-don! All humanity VTuber...
全人類？！ ちがうちがう！
All humanity?! No, no!
間違えちゃった！ もう1回ね！
I messed up! One more time, okay?
いきます！
Here I go!
とどんとどんとんどん！ 全VTuberの中で一番可愛いのは誰だー？！
To-don to-don ton-don! Out of all VTubers, who is the cutest?!
とどんとどんとんどん！
To-don to-don ton-don!
ぺこーらー！
Pekora!
よーし！できました！ありがとう！
Alright! We did it! Thank you!
じゃあ次はフレア！
Next up is Flare!
はーい！じゃあフレアは「はい、ダーリン！」って言うので、「はい、ハニー！」って返してください！
Yes! I will say "Hi, darling!", so please respond with "Hi, honey!"
オッケー！
Okay!
いきますよ！
Here I go!
はい、ダーリン！
Hi, darling!
はい、ハニー！
Hi, honey!
ありがとうー！ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアです！そして？
Thank you! I'm Shiranui Flare of hololive 3rd Gen! And next?
はい！えー、どうしようかな...じゃあ「こんまっする！」って言うから普通に「こんまっする！」って...
Yes! Um, what should I do... Well, I'll say "Kon-muscle!", so just respond with "Kon-muscle!"...
「牛丼」もいいよ？牛丼もね、牛丼はまあ...あ、やばいやばい！
You can do "Beef bowl" too? Beef bowl is, well... Ah, wait, no, no!
あぶないあぶない！
That was close!
いくぞ！せーの！
Here we go! One, two!
こんまっする！
Kon-muscle!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！はい！そして？
Yes, I'm Shirogane Noel of hololive 3rd Gen! Yes! And next?
きみたち！本物のパイパイ仮面は誰ー？！
You guys! Who is the real Pai Pai Kamen?!
ノエル！ ノエル！
Noel! Noel!
ノエルがパイパイ仮面だ！
Noel is Pai Pai Kamen!
ちょっと！昨日からさ、ぺこらに船長取られるし、ノエルにパイパイ仮面...
Wait a minute! Since yesterday, Pekora took my captain role, and Noel is Pai Pai Kamen...
船長ですかい？！本物のパイパイ仮面はノエルに奪われたわけですね！
Are you the Captain?! So the real Pai Pai Kamen was stolen by Noel!
悲しい...ということでね、はい！
How sad... Anyway, yes!
はい、ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Yes, I'm Houshou Marine, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, hololive 3rd Gen!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ついにDay 2！昨日と衣装違くない？
Finally Day 2! Isn't our outfit different from yesterday?
あれ？わかりましたか皆さん！
Oh? Did everyone notice?!
悪魔になっちゃった！
We turned into devils!
天使から悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？そうなんですよね！
We went from angels to looking like devils? That's right!
実はこれ、初めて公開するんですよ！
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this!
みんなびっくりしたかな？
Was everyone surprised?
可愛い！ありがとう！
Cute! Thank you!
え、でも悪魔、マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで、かなり親和性あるかも
Well, but as for devils, Marine sells herself as a little devil type, so it fits perfectly.
ぺこらも小悪魔系でやってるから親和性ある！
Pekora is also doing the little devil thing, so it fits me too!
変な悪魔いかない？変な悪魔
Don't do weird devils, okay? Weird devils...
天使と悪魔どっちが好き、きみたち？
Which do you guys like better, angels or devils?
あ、確かに！じゃあペンライトで言ってもらえば？
Ah, true! Why don't you have them show us with their penlights?
ペンライトの色？白と赤かな？
The penlight colors? White and red, maybe?
じゃあ、悪魔派は赤！天使派は白！
Then, the devil faction is red! The angel faction is white!
じゃあ皆さん変えてください！ペンライト振って！
Alright, everyone, please change your colors! Wave your penlights!
あ、でも結構いい感じに割れてる？若干赤が多いか？
Ah, but it's split pretty well? Is red slightly more?
え、悪魔の方が人気？いやでも結構白も多いよ
Oh, are devils more popular? No, but there are quite a lot of white lights too.
すげえー！ありがとう！
Amazing! Thank you!
じゃあ今日いいね、悪魔な感じも！
Well, today is great, the devil vibe is nice too!
これを見せられて良かったね！
I'm glad we could show you this!
そしてDay 1に引き続き、バンドも生演奏となっております！
And continuing from Day 1, we also have a live band performing!
いぇーい！生演奏ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you for the live performance!
すっごいかっこいいですね、これね！
It's really cool, isn't it?
かっこいい！ありがとうございます！嬉しいです。
Cool! Thank you very much! We're so happy.
そして配信のコメントももちろん見えてます！
And of course, we can see the stream comments too!
見えてるよー！みんなー！
We can see you! Everyone!
もちろん、会場のみんなももちろん！見えてるよー！
Of course, everyone at the venue too! We see you!
みんなの素敵な気合いの入った、推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとー！
Thanks for wearing your wonderful fan outfits!
ありがとー！可愛いー！
Thank you! So cute!
最高、最高ですよ！最高ですね！
It's awesome, absolutely awesome! It really is!
でも、しょっぱなね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけど...
But starting off, we had that shuffle medley...
そうよ、そうよ！びっくりしたよね！
That's right, that's right! You were surprised, right?
アゲアゲ！でもですね、なんとですね、ここまでで...
Super hyped! But, you see, incredibly, up to here...
え？冒頭無料チラ見せが...
Huh? The free opening preview...
終了となります！えー！？嘘でしょ！？
...has come to an end! What?! You're kidding, right?!
そんなこと...嘘ペコでしょうが？
No way... You're lying, peko, right?
嘘ではないペコです...
It's not a lie, peko...
みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、概要欄に配信チケットのリンクがあるので...
Since I'm sure you want to watch, the stream ticket link is in the description...
今！ポチポチっと買ってみてください！
...so please try clicking and buying it right now!
お願いします！
Please!
後悔はさせない！今日はすごいから！今日も！
We won't regret it! Today is going to be amazing! Today too!
もっとすごくなってます！
It's gotten even more incredible!
ぶち上げぶち上げで！そう！
Let's get totally hyped! Yes!
Day 1とは違った盛り上がりだね。そう！
It's a different kind of hype from Day 1. Yes!
君たちも今日、超ぶち上がりなんで、頑張って最後まで息切れしないように、ぶち上がってください！
You guys are also super hyped today, so hang in there, don't run out of breath, and get totally hyped until the very end!
最後だから、しっかり声出してね！出してね！
Since it's the end, make sure to let your voices out! Let it out!
そして配信で楽しんでる人は、ハッシュタグ「きゅるるん大作戦Day2」でいっぱい呟いてください！
And those enjoying the stream, please tweet a lot with the hashtag "Kyururun Daisakusen Day 2"!
お願いします！
Please!
ドキドキするね。
My heart is pounding.
いいですか？行きます？次の曲に行ってもいいでしょうか？
Are you ready? Shall we go? Can we move on to the next song?
行きましょう！次の曲はなんと、私からスタートさせていただきます！
Let's go! The next song, incredibly, will start with me!
おおー！何が来るのかな？
Ooh! What's coming?
次の曲行きましょう！きゅるるんメドレー！
Let's go to the next song! Kyururun Medley!
おー！
Ooh!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！